I woke up at 2:40 on Independence Day
because there is a rally in our school in
which I am dressed as Radha Rani and it takes a
lot of time to get into her getup, so
I could not sleep the whole night.  So first of all,
after brushing etc., I started doing
my makeup.  First I applied
primer and then I remembered that I have to
wear lenses too, which made me cry.
Then I applied a lot of foundation and then
did eye shadow makeup.  And the strongest thing
I was going to apply was eyelashes.
I don't wear lashes so I wasn't sure whether
I should wear them or not.  Then
I also did forehead makeup with alta.  And
you know, since last year itself I had decided
that next year I wish I would become Radha Rani
and this time I did become one and I had done my hair
yesterday but within a short time it became
normal again and I had ordered this jewellery from Myntra
which I liked very much
and whatever I am using
I will tag it and
I had also ordered this cute lehenga from Myntra.  There were 100
lehengas but out of them, mom and I
liked this one.  And this is my final look.
Now we are going for the rally.  In many places the
rally has been cancelled due to rain.
But still a rally was held in Lohaghat.  That's all for today's
blog, see you
in the next part.  And yes, Happy Independence Day.